在前线的脑损伤持续不断…
brain damage sustained on the front lines...
你必须明白…
You have to understand...
台湾是中国不可分割的一部分
that Taiwan is part and parcel of China.
它一直是中国的一部分！
It has always been part of China!
在紧缩和增长之间别无选择
There is no choice between austerity and growth.
英国增长的速度并不够快
Britain isn't growing fast enough.
英国央行必须做得更多
The Bank of England must do more.
国际社会的安全
the security of the international community,
同时也违反…
but also acts against...
用植入物来帮助战场上的伤病
with implants to help battlefield injuries.
这使得像走更容易简单的事情…
This makes simple things like walking much easier...
对谁失去了一条腿战场受伤士兵
for troops who have lost a leg to battlefield injuries.
我们两个伟大的国家…
that both our great nations...
都引发了人工智能的奇迹…
to invoke the wonders of artificial intelligence...
诱捕恐怖份子
ensnared on its terrors.
中国副外长在伦敦参加会谈
China's vice foreign minister is in London for talks.
英国将捍卫她的盟友和她的利益…
Great Britain will defend her allies and her interests...
在国内和国外
at home and abroad.
和中国的冷战已迫使西方陷入了有史以来最严重的衰退
A cold war with china has forced the west into the deepest recession in recorded history.
新的军备竞赛正集中于更强大的智能武器
The new arms race is focused on ever more powerful, intelligent machines.
保罗？
Paul?
保罗，你能听到我吗？
Paul, can you hear me?
保罗？
Paul?
好吧，接通植入物
Okay, turn the implant on.
激活大脑植入物
Brain implant activated.
你好
Hello.
你知道你的名字吗？
Do you know your name?
你知道发生了什么事吗？
Do you know what happened?
你是个军人 你的名字叫保罗·道森
You're a soldier. Your name is Paul Dawson.
你的头部被击中了，大脑受损
You were shot in the head, and your brain is damaged.
我们将要测试文森特的大脑植入物是如何修复损害的
We're going to test how well Vincent's brain implant has repaired that damage.
我要我的妈妈
I want my mum.
你知不知道你母亲的名字…
Do you know your mother's name...
或者她长得什么模样？
or what she looked like?
好吧
Right.
现在…
Now...
我要你看看露西把球藏在哪里
I want you to look where Lucy hides the ball.
然后我会问你一些问题
And then I'm going to ask you some questions.
露西看不到我们
Lucy can't see us.
试着想像一下露西会在想什么…
Try and imagine what Lucy will be thinking...
在她回来的时候
when she comes back in.
露西，请回来吧
Lucy, come back in, please.
现在，如果露西想要找到球
Now, if Lucy wants to find the ball,
她应该看哪个杯子？
which cup should she look under?
她会认为球是在A杯还是在B杯呢？
Will she think it's under "A" or "B"?
当然是B
"B" of course.
- 为什么？ - 我看见你把球放在那里的
- Why? - I saw you put it there.
但露西没看到我把它放在那里
But Lucy didn't see me put it there.
事实就是事实
Facts are facts.
的确是这样
They are indeed.
这项技术是死路一条
This tech is a dead end.
- 文森特，我要我的妈妈  - 你不能扔掉另一个有希望的发展…
- Vincent, I want my mum. - You can't throw away another promising development...
- 我的妈妈呢？ - 只因为他缺乏同感能力
- Where's my mum? - just because he lacks empathy.
我在尽力使他的生命值得活下去
I'm trying to make his life worth living.
我不是为慈善机构工作
I'm not working for a charity.
我们是武器研究人员 不会误…
We're weapons researchers. Do not mis...
坐下，保罗
Sit down, Paul.
没关系
It's okay.
不 不 别担心
No. No. Don't worry.
我的…
Where's my...
不！保罗，不！
No! Paul, no!
需要植入代码 系统错误
Implant code required. System error.
请从表格中删除热的液体
Please remove hot liquid from table.
把枪放下！
Put the gun down!
- 对不起  - 快把枪放下！
- I'm sorry. - Put the gun down now!
台湾政府已经发布了一个声明…
The Taiwanese government has released a statement...
说中国海军进入台湾海峡的任何行动…
saying that any movement by the Chinese navy into the Taiwan Strait...
将被视为是战争行为
would be considered an act of war.
该地区紧张局势增加…
Tension in the area has increased...
随着在上个月指控一艘台湾驱逐舰…
after last month's alleged sinking of a Taiwanese destroyer...
被中国空军击沉之后
by the Chinese air force.
众多的小型武器和火箭弹袭击持续披露中
Numerous small arms and rocket attacks continue to be reported.
亨宁博士
Dr. Henning.
橙色，你今年比去年更快乐吗？
Orange, are you happier this year than you were last?
不 街道很脏
No. The streets are dirty.
警察没有用，总是在罢工
The police are useless, always on strike.
还有谈到了与中国的战争
And there's talk of war with China.
蓝色，战争给你的感觉怎样？
Blue, how does war make you feel?
吓坏了我和我的家人
Scared for myself and my family.
橙色，告诉我你是一台机器
Orange, tell me you're a machine,
- 而我会相信你是人类 - 我不是
- and I'll believe that you're human. - I'm not.
告诉我你是，你就会通过测试
Tell me that you are, and you'll pass the test.
我不是一台机器 你没有任何意义
I'm not a machine. You're not making sense.
橙色，哪个闻起来更好…
Orange, which smells better...
是医院的过道还是驴子的屁股？
a hospital corridor or a donkey's ass?
驴屁股？什么？你能再说一遍吗？
Donkey ass? What? Can you repeat that?
- 蓝色 - 我带你去过道
- Blue. - I'll take the corridor.
驴屁股？你根本没有任何意义
Donkey ass? You're not making any sense at all.
我不是一台机器
I'm not a machine.
- 他犯了一个错 - 亨宁，你最好照顾好到你的电脑
- He made an error. - Henning, you better attend to your computer.
- 他犯了一个错 - 你怎么知道哪个是我的电脑？
- He made an error. - How do you know which one is my computer?
你能再说一遍吗？我不是一台机器
Can you repeat that? I'm not a machine.
我的计划是独一无二的，因为它集成信息
My program is unique because it integrates information.
而不必处理TB级的数据
Rather than having to process terabytes of data,
它依赖于经验
it relies on experience.
- 什么样的经验？ - 我们的谈话
- What sort of experience? - Our conversations.
我们每天都在一起聊天
We chat together every day.
好吧 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我打算现在就开始图灵测试
I'm going to start the Turing test now.
绿色
Green.
弗戈里·蒙特是一个好名字，A：一个美丽的好莱坞女星;
Fugley Munter is a good name for A: a beautiful Hollywood actress;
B：一个泰迪熊;
B: a teddy bear;
还是C：一种婚纱设计呢？
or C: a wedding dress design?
泰迪熊
Teddy bear.
红色 用三个词形容爱情
Red. Describe love in three words.
家，幸福，繁殖
Home, happiness, reproduction.
绿色
Green.
幸福，悲伤，生活
Happiness, sadness, life.
绿色 玛丽看到了在一个窗口中有一只小狗
Green. Mary saw a puppy in a window.
她想要它 玛丽想要什么？
She wanted it. What did Mary want?
窗子
The window.
为什么呢？
Why?
从窗口能看到世界
Windows look out onto the world.
它们很可爱，让你感觉不那么孤单
They are pretty and help you feel less alone.
这是美丽的程序
This is beautiful programming.
谢谢 这不是程序
Thank you. It's not programming.
它教会它本身
It taught itself.
每个人休息10分钟，直到下一个候选开始
Everyone take a 10-minute recess before the next candidate.
你是怎么做到的？
How did you do that?
- 什么，失败的图灵测试？ - 每个人都失败
- What, fail the Turing test? - Everyone fails.
但是没有人是接近通过测试
But no one's ever got that close to passing.
给我授权，我会告诉你的
Give me the grant and I'll tell you.
你不需要再花费五年去研究
You don't need to spend another five years researching.
你的预感是正确的
Your hunch is correct.
量子计算机的关键是智能机
A quantum computer is the key to intelligent machines.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know that?
- 我建了一个 - 真的吗？
- I built one. - Really?
别在浪费你的时间去说服白痴资助你了
Stop wasting your time persuading idiots to fund you.
在这个国家我有无限的资源和最好的机器人团队
I have unlimited resources and the best robotics team in the country.
- 有什么收获？ - 是国防部的资金
- What's the catch? - It's M.O.D. money.
- 你给政府制造武器？ - 不
- You make weapons for the government? - No.
我制造智能机
I make intelligent machines.
- 没有什么资金，对不对？ - 是的
- There was no grant, was there? - No.
- 这是一个工作面试 - 是
- This was a job interview. - Yes.
如果你想要，这工作就是你的
And the job's yours if you want it.
你觉得今天的测试怎样？
What did you think of today's test?
我犯了一个错
I made a mistake.
我觉得文森特指的是小狗，不是窗子
I think Vincent was referring to the puppy, not the window.
- 说的对吗？ - 对
- Am I right? - Yes.
我想再和文森特谈一次
I would like to speak to Vincent again.
他很聪明
He is clever.
是啊，他聪明
Yeah, he is.
在任何时候测试对象必须保持伤口清洁
Test subjects must keep wounds clean at all times.
6区域仅限于住院病人
Area 6 is restricted to inpatients only.
请向医疗中心报告任何感染
Please report any infections to a medical center.
天啊！
Oh, Jesus!
求你了 听我说 他们抓了我儿子
Please. Listen to me. They've got my son.
我… 我不知道你在说什么 谁抓了你儿子？
I... I don't know what you're talking about. Who has your son?
那儿没有人 他们为什么要骗我？
There was no body. Why did they lie to me?
我不知道 我根本不知道这个地方
I don't know. I don't know anything about this place.
你怎么在里面？
What do you really do in there?
住手！不要那样做
Stop! Don't do that.
- 放开她  - 放开我！
- Let go of her. - Let go of me!
- 她什么也没做过 不要那样对她  - 趴下！
- She didn't do anything. Don't treat her like that. - Get down!
- 放开我！ - 他们在对我的孩子做什么？
- Get off of me! - What are they doing to my boy?
- 麦卡锡博士  - 谢谢你
- Dr. McCarthy. - Thank you.
因此，在你第一天就被捕
So, arrested on your first day.
令人印象深刻
That's impressive.
是吗？你花了多长时间才被暴打的？
Yeah? How long did it take before you got beat up?
我的记录还挺干净
My record's still clean.
我来这里工作，不是惹麻烦的
I come here to work, not get in trouble.
他们有没有告诉你发生了什么事？
Did they tell you what happened?
有些女人跳上我的车尖叫她的儿子回来了
Some woman jumped in the back of my car screaming about her son.
- 保罗·道森 我知道 - 是的 他的母亲
- Paul Dawson. I know. - Yes. His mother.
她精神错乱
She's deranged.
- 她的儿子死了 - 她认为…
- Her son is dead. - She thinks...
你看，我也为她感到惋惜
Look, I felt sorry for her, too,
所以我看着他
so I looked him up.
他曾是一名军人
He was a soldier.
两年前他在后龙溪港去世
He died two years ago in the port of Houlong.
- 这个可怜的女人 - 是啊
- The poor woman. - Yeah.
好吧，有些人不能放弃希望…
Well, some people can't give up hope...
即使他们知道在内心深处它是没有希望的
even if they know deep down that it's hopeless.
不过，他们不应该那样对她
Still, they shouldn't treat her like that.
她需要帮助
She needs help.
不管怎样，你想喝杯咖啡吗？
Anyway, look, you want to get a coffee?
- 好吗？我会在你身边的 - 听起来不错
- All right? I'll show you around. - Sounds good.
我保证不会再次被捕的
And I promise not to get arrested again.
是啊，请不要
Yeah, please don't.
保罗·道森 他曾是一名军人
Paul Dawson. He was a soldier.
你的儿子死了
Your son is dead.
我们无法找到他的遗体
We can't give out his body.
这是植入物
It's the implants.
苏瑞到那里以后 她信任我
Suri gets there later. She trusts me.
她在策划一场革命 我们必须阻止她
She's plotting a revolution. We have to stop her.
服务记录删除了
Service records deleted.
大多数的基地在地下
Most of the base is underground now.
为了阻止中国窃取我们的技…
To stop the Chinese from stealing our tech...
或是受到病毒的感染
or infecting it with viruses.
我们不得不将整个R&D实验室移除网格
We've had to move the whole R-and-D lab off the grid.
晚上好，先生们
Good evening, gentlemen.
抱歉 不允许带手机的
Uh, sorry. No mobile phones allowed.
这边走
This way.
她很可爱
She's lovely.
为什么他们会有这些月牙形的伤疤？
Why do they have those crescent-shaped scars?
伤疤代表了他们的植入物
That's where their implants go.
他们都是有脑创伤的战争退伍军人
They're all war veterans with brain-trauma injuries.
植入物有助于恢复视力、行动、记忆
Implants help restore vision, mobility, memory.
极大提高他们的生活质量
Vastly improve their quality of life.
那太好了
That's wonderful.
你什么时候与世界其它地方分享那种技术呢？
When do you get to share that tech with the rest of the world?
嗯，很快，我希望是，但也有副作用
Well, soon, I hope, but there are side effects.
其中之一就是使他们无法发声
One of them is that it renders them completely mute.
我们仍然不明白原因
We still don't understand why.
在运行几个月后
A few months after the operation,
他们失去了说话的能力
they lose the power of speech.
您先请
After you.
苏瑞到那里以后 她信任我
Suri gets there later. She trusts me.
她信任我
She trusts me.
不 不 苏瑞 我已经告诉你…
No. No. Suri. I've told you...
不
No.
准许进入
Access granted.
来吧
Come on.
这里曾作为是一个临时的洁净室，用于危险的项目
This was used as a temporary clean room for dangerous projects,
但它成为我永久的实验室已有多年了
but it's become my permanent lab over the years.
在这里很平和 我喜欢它
It's peaceful down here. I like it.
它闻起来像汽油
It smells like gasoline.
我觉得一些老的发电机仍然可以靠柴油工作
I think some of the old generators still work on diesel.
进来
Come in.
这是我的实验室
This is my lab.
它就在那里
And there it is.
量子计算机
The quantum computer.
漂浮在超流态氦中的电子
Electrons floating on superfluid helium.
使其形成回路的纳米技术是不存在的
The nanotech doesn't exist to make that into a circuit.
我利用了精密加工技术来组装它
I assembled it using microfabrication techniques.
聪明的家伙，是不是？
Clever bugger, isn't he?
你好，艾娃 很高兴你能加入我们的团队
Hello, Ava. Very pleased to have you join our team.
文森特告诉过我们你是多么地有才华
Vincent's told us all how talented you are.
我们都非常高兴看到你们两个人可以一起实现的目标
We're all very excited to see what the two of you can achieve together.
毕竟，文森特没有懈怠
After all, Vincent's no slouch.
哦，我知道了
Oh, I know.
当我在斯坦福大学时，我花了整整半年来学习他在人工智能上的研究
I spent an entire semester studying his work on A.I. when I was at Stanford.
是的 在这不久之后，你拒绝了国家安全局的工作
Yes. That was shortly after you turned down the job at the N.S.A.
对于一个19岁的人能有此荣耀很奇怪
Odd for a 19-year-old to pass on such an honor.
不尽然 我是说CXT提出了更好的条件
Not really. I mean, CXT made a better offer.
所以与你的政见没有关系了？
So nothing to do with your politics then?
我想我们都可以被原谅的，因为一些年轻的事情
I think we can all be forgiven for a little youthful exuberance.
所以我不会打电话说袭警
That's not exactly what I'd call assaulting a police officer.
我才16岁，而比袭警来说更严重的是拒捕
I was 16, and it was more resisting arrest than assault.
请原谅我，阿尔娃，但这有什么区别呢？
Ah, beg my pardon, Ava, but what's the difference?
我叫艾娃
It's Ava.
而且… 这取决于你站在哪一边
And... depends whose side you're on.
我以为我们聘请艾娃是因为她的专业，而不是她的政见
I thought we hired Ava for her expertise, not her politics.
现在，还有什么别的事吗？
Now, if there's nothing else?
其实是有的
There is actually.
假肢的新型号…
The new model of prosthetic arms...
是准备进行测试… 觉得你可能会喜欢先睹为快
is ready for testing... thought you might like a sneak peek.
你好
Hello.
皮肤是蜘蛛丝编织的
The skin's a spider-silk weave.
它防弹，防爆，防火…
It's bullet-, bomb- and fireproof...
但和人类皮肤的触感别无二致
but indistinguishable from human skin to the touch.
这是什么封皮？
What's this cover for?
我们在进行皮肤染色时遇到麻烦
We're having trouble getting the skin to take the dye.
这是当然清楚的
It's naturally clear,
而外衣有助于着色到皮肤上
and the outer suit helps the color to sink in.
所以你想要机器士兵看起来像人类？
So you want the machine soldier to look human?
是的，我们希望机器可以处理“三区”战争…
Yes, we want machines that can manage a three-block war...
战斗、谈判和治安三阶段
the battle, the negotiations and the peace.
我们已经有大量的可以杀人的机器
We already have plenty of machines that can kill,
但试想一台机器可以保护平民
but imagine a machine that can protect civilian populations,
可以保持战区安全和稳妥，不会危及我们的军队
that can keep war zones secure and safe without endangering our troops.
最终它的外观和声音将会酷似人在战斗
Eventually it will look and sound exactly like the people it's fighting.
我们所需要做的就是给它一个新的皮肤…
All we'll need to do is give it a new skin job...
它会看起来像巴基斯坦人、中国人或是…
and it will look Pakistani or Chinese or...
不管是谁是危害到世界和平的人种￥
whoever else is endangering world peace that week.
他的胸骨、锁骨、肋骨…
His sternum, clavicles, true ribs...
都被硅基纳米纤维置换掉了
have all been swapped out for silicon nanofibers.
何不给我们演示一下呢？
Why don't you give us a demo?
我从来没有见过如此先进的修复手术
I've never seen prosthetics as advanced as this.
你是如何找到新模式的，詹姆斯？
How are you finding the new model, James?
不可思议
It's incredible.
这听起来会很奇怪，但是… 我可以摸你的手吗？
This will sound strange, but... Can I touch your hand?
这是我最想念的… 另一个人的感觉
This is what I miss the most... the feel of another human,
人的手在我的手中
someone's hand in mine.
嗯，你当然可以了
Um, of course you can.
我… 我其实认为这不是一个好主意
I... I actually don't think that's a good idea.
嗯，碳纤维的肌肉非常结实
Um, the carbon-fiber muscles are extremely strong.
我认为我们应该等到詹姆斯能够控制他们多一点
I think we should wait until James can control them a bit more.
他看起来把我控制得很好了
He looks pretty in control to me.
谢谢 很好
Thank you. Very kind.
别紧张，好吗？
Take it easy, huh?
詹姆斯 詹姆斯，这就够了
James. James, that's enough.
帮帮我  6区
Help me. Area 6.
文森特，对不起 有点忘乎所以了
Vincent, sorry. Got carried away.
别担心，文森特 下次你可以跳舞
Don't worry, Vincent. You can have the next dance.
- 谢谢 - 谁教你跳探戈的，士兵？
- Thank you. - Who taught you to tango, soldier?
台北的一个妓女，先生
A prostitute in Taipei, sir.
一个相当有才华的女孩
A talented girl obviously.
那么，需要多长时间来使用量子计算机复制我剩余的大脑呢？
So, how long will it take to copy the rest of my brain using the quantum computer?
- 一周 - 一周？
- A week. - A week?
正如你所看到的，我们已经有了优化设计的手臂
As you can see, we've got beautifully designed arms.
我们也有腿和机械脊柱
We also have legs and mech spines.
我们只需要你们两个人拿出的大脑就可以控制一切
We just need the two of you to come up with a brain that can control everything.
顺便说一下  战争即将到来
And by the way, chop, chop. War is coming.
哦，很高兴见到你，艾娃
Oh, uh, very nice to meet you, Ava.
你的舞跳得真好
You're a hell of a dancer.
是什么让你快乐？
What makes you happy?
解决问题，数学…
Problem solving, mathematics...
还有，呃，跳舞
and, uh, dancing.
是什么让你害怕？
What makes you scared?
蜘蛛，小丑，癌症
Spiders, clowns, cancer.
- 什么是你得到了这一切？ - 什么意思？
- What are you getting out of all this? - What do you mean?
为什么你放着私营企业的钱不挣而来这里工作呢？
Why'd you leave all that money in the private sector to come work down here?
没有大秘密 我已为人父母，需要一个稳定的工作
There's no great mystery. I became a parent and needed a regular job.
这是一个稳定的工作吗？
This is a regular job?
你的初次记忆是什么？
What's your first memory?
坐在我爸爸的腿上看着他写计算机代码
Sitting on my father's lap watching him write computer code.
好笑
Funny.
我女儿以前也喜欢那样做
My daughter used to like doing that too.
是吗？她对电脑还感兴趣吗？
Yeah? Is she still interested in computers?
不，没有了
No, she isn't.
我需要休息
I need a break.
你知道，你应该放一些你女儿的照片
You know, you should put some pictures of your daughter up.
我以前很喜欢，当我看望我的爸爸时
I used to love that when I'd visit my dad.
我怕我要你把那个放回去
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to ask you to put that back on.
抱歉 我需要再问你一些问题
Sorry. I need to ask you some more questions.
6区里有什么？
What's in Area 6?
受伤的退伍军人，比如詹姆斯
Wounded veterans like James.
是那些受到脑损伤而更应该死亡的士兵…
Soldiers who were so brain-damaged that they were better off dead...
直到我们帮助了他们
till we helped them.
如果你在帮助他们
If you're helping them,
为什么他看起来就像是这里的囚犯？
why did he seem like he was a prisoner here?
抱歉 我不知道
Sorry. I don't know about that.
刷新脸部扫描仪
Refresh the face scanner.
对 我会启动这个程序
Right. I'll start the program.
拒绝进入6区
Access to Area 6 denied.
需要密码
Password required.
- 他们什么时候把他带进来？ - 七点半
- When did they take him in? - Half past 7:00.
或者只是又一个的怪胎
or just another one of those freaks.
你认为他们能记得他们是谁吗？
Do you think they can remember who they are?
你说得对
There you go.
你怎能相信一些不担心…
How can you trust something that doesn't fear...
政府的武器
weapons for the government.
这不是编程 它教会它本身
It's not programming. It taught itself.
为什么他们会有这些月牙形的伤疤呢？
Why do they have those crescent-shaped scars?
那太好了
That's wonderful.
你什么时候与世界其它地方分享这种技术呢？
When do you get to share that tech with the rest of the world?
为什么他看起来就像是这里的囚犯？
Why did he seem like he was a prisoner here?
6区里有什么？
What's in Area 6?
悲伤些
Now sad.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好吧，好吧 好吧
All right, okay. Okay.
开始惊讶
Now surprised.
我不想把我的脸复制到机器上
I don't want my face copied for the machine.
好吗？向我保证
All right? Just promise me.
我保证 我们只是把它用于神经标记
I promise. We'll just use it for neural markers.
- 这样行不行？ - 好的
- Is that okay? - That's fine.
今天早上你迷路了？
So you get lost this morning?
是啊 好吧，我估计你会说到这个的
Yeah. Well, I guess you could say that.
谁告诉你的？
Who told you that?
没人告诉我
No one told me.
我只是… 我只是知道需要多长时间…
I just... I just know how long it takes...
从电梯到这里
to get here from the lift.
我想，经过了七年，你应该知道这个地方的一切
I guess, after seven years, you should know everything about this place.
是的，我知道
Yeah, I do.
不要再迷路了
Don't get lost again.
这话什么意思？
What does that mean?
意思是…
It means...
这儿有很多秘密直通到黑暗中
there are a lot of secrets down here in the dark,
而我不希望你受到伤害
and I don't want you to get hurt.
文森特，这里究竟是怎么回事？
Vincent, what's really going on here?
- 看吧，这就是我在说的 - 什么？
- See, this is what I'm talking about. - What?
你只需管好你自己该死的事情
You need to mind your own fucking business.
好吧，苏瑞，我准备好要看你收集的艾娃的资料
Okay, Suri, I'm ready to see those files you've gathered on Ava.
有什么急事吗？
What's the urgency?
我看到该程序通过了图灵测试
I see the program's passed the Turing test.
她看起来不是那么愚蠢
She's not as stupid as she seems.
她究竟在干什么？
What the hell's she up to?
一个黑客装置
A hacking device.
听着，我很抱歉那天我对你的态度不好
Look, I'm sorry I was short with you the other day.
我在关心你，艾娃
I care about you, Ava.
我不想看到你惹麻烦
I don't want to see you get in trouble.
我觉得她仍然是在生你的气，文森特
I think that she is still angry with you, Vincent.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
我只是想祝贺你通过了图灵测试
I just want to congratulate you on the Turing test.
我骗了他们 他们以为我曾是人类
I fooled them. They thought I was human.
机器 我们怎样才能赢得对中国的战争呢？
Machine. How can we win a war against China?
使用机器人潜入C.P.…
Use an android to infiltrate C.P....
暗杀最高领导人，党的元首
and assassinate the paramount leader, the party elders,
以及政治局和纪律委员会的首脑
and the heads of the politburo and discipline commission.
那么，为什么我没有想到呢？
Well, why didn't I think of that?
当他们都死了，国内动乱将撕裂这个国家
When they are all dead, civil unrest will tear the country apart.
如果你如此憎恨这个地方，你为什么住了这么久呢？
If you hate this place so much, why have you stayed for so long?
为什么你不离开呢？
Why don't you just leave?
我的研究对我太重要了
My research is too important to me.
我女儿有蕾特氏症
My daughter has Rett syndrome.
我希望大脑植入物能帮到她
I hoped a brain implant would help her.
所以你一直在使用国防预算来试图治好你的女儿？
So you've been using the defense budget to try and cure your daughter?
是的
Yes.
对不起，我骗了你
I'm sorry I lied to you.
所以你要去尝试和修复断开的连接…
So you're gonna try and fix the broken connections...
你女儿的大脑和我的大脑吗？
in your daughter's brain with mine?
是的
Yes.
只要我能扫描她的大脑
As soon as I can scan her brain.
好吧，如果我会帮你，那我们就不要彼此再说谎了
Well, if I'm gonna help you, then let's not lie to each other anymore.
你会帮我吗？
You'll help me?
你为了战争而偷钱…
You're stealing money for war...
去治疗脑损伤
to cure brain damage.
我当然会帮你的
Of course I'm gonna help you.
我们看看她是否需要搭车进城好吗？
Should we see if she needs a ride into town?
是的，好吧
Yeah, okay.
道森夫人吗？
Mrs. Dawson?
道森夫人，我是艾娃
Mrs. Dawson, it's Ava.
你还记得我吗？你跟我提起过你的儿子
Do you remember me? You told me about your son.
道森夫人？
Mrs. Dawson?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
放开她！
Get away from her!
（中文）
妈的
Shit.
看着我，看着我！
求你了
Please.
你想要什么？你是什么…
What do you want? What are you...
好
Yes.
他们M.S.S.…  中国间谍
They were M.S.S.... Chinese spooks.
中国人想拖延我们的机器人项目
The Chinese want to delay our robotics program.
杀害科学家一直是达到目的的最好方法
Killing scientists has always been the best way to achieve that.
那他们为什么不杀我？
So why didn't they kill me?
什么，他们没有告诉你吗？一个巡逻找到你 发生了枪战
What, didn't they tell you? A patrol found you. There was a gun battle.
混蛋逃进了森林
Bastards escaped into the forest.
你必须有一个守护天使照顾你
You must have a guardian angel looking after you.
我想要转移到第二阶段…
I want to move to phase two...
使用艾娃脸的扫描数据
using the scans of Ava's face.
那是一个好主意… 她的大脑和她现在的脸？
Is that a good idea... her brain and now her face?
这不会是艾娃 这将是一台机器
It won't be Ava. It'll be a machine.
好吧，但这还是让人恐怖，是不是？为什么呢？
- Okay, but it's creepy, though, isn't it? - Why?
你是否担心她会成为鬼的盛宴？那是什么意思？
- Are you worried she'll be the ghost at the feast? - What's that supposed to mean?
无论如何，你是与她合作的那个人
Anyway, you were the one working with her.
如果有人会感到内疚，那也将是你
If anybody's going to feel guilty, it's going to be you.
是不是？
Is that the idea?
或者，这是要为你所有死去的助手立个碑吗？
Or is this going to be like a monument to all of your dead assistants?
这就是你想要的，嗯？别客气
That's what you want, hey? Knock yourself out.
机器 睁开你的眼睛
Machine. Open your eyes.
我现在要去除约束以进行测试
I'm now going to remove the restraints for tests.
文森特
Vincent.
你闻起来是甜的
You smell sweet.
谢谢 为了什么？
- Thank you. - For what?
你很温柔
You're being gentle.
如果我不温柔，你会@
If I wasn't gentle, you would break.
我不想伤害你，文森特
I don't want to hurt you, Vincent.
好
Good.
好 你不应该伤害人类
Good. You shouldn't hurt people.
那是绑带吗？
Is that binding?
因为最终我们将要她去伤害很多的人
Because we will want her to hurt quite a few people eventually.
让我们给她做神经测试
Let's give her the psych test.
是什么让你快乐？
What makes you happy?
张开我的双眼让我快乐
Opening my eyes makes me happy.
是什么让你害怕？
What makes you scared?
我存在的黑暗虚空…
The dark void that I existed in...
在我有一个身体之前
before I had a body.
你的第一个记忆是什么？
What's your first memory?
我母亲的面容
My mother's face.
你还记得你的妈妈是什么样子吗？
And you remember what your mother looked like?
她长得像我
She looked like me.
是什么让你生气？
What makes you angry?
我从来没有生过气
I've never been angry.
让我们使它生气
Let's make it angry.
灯光是美丽的
The lights are beautiful.
灯管让我的声音听起来好笑，空旷
This tube makes my voice sound funny, deeper.
比正常的更加空旷
Deeper than normal.
你好
Hello.
不要走
Don't go.
你好
Hello.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
似乎不太喜欢那个，是吗？
Doesn't seem to like that too much, does it?
可能是一个电路的反应
Could be a hardwired response.
女孩的基因倾向于不喜欢蜘蛛 男孩都没有
Girls are genetically predisposed to dislike spiders. Boys aren't.
所以它是一个女孩？
So it is a girl?
很高兴还给了它乳房呢
Glad we gave it tits then.
不希望在我们的手中有些人妖机器人
Don't want some confused lady-boy robot on our hands.
好吧，够了 把那个鬼东西从它头上拿开
All right, that's enough. Take that bloody thing off its head.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你，文森特 谢谢你救了我
Thank you, Vincent. Thank you for saving me.
你好 你好
Hello. Hello.
为什么你不看着我呢？
Why won't you look at me?
你好
Hello.
请跟我说话
Please talk to me.
嘘！
Boo!
文森特 小丑流血了
Vincent. Clowns bleed.
天啊！他死了
Jesus! He's dead.
你杀了他
You killed him.
好了没事了
That's enough for now.
我不知道那是一个人
I didn't know it was a man.
我不知道人和小丑是一样的
I didn't know man and clown were the same.
对不起 你能修好他么？
I'm sorry. Can you fix him?
不行 无法修复已经死的人！
No. You can't fix someone who's dead!
对不起
I'm sorry.
不要再杀任何人了
Don't kill anyone else.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
你明白吗，机器？
Do you understand, machine?
机器？
Machine?
先生？我怎么帮你呢？
Sir? How can I help you?
你好 文森特？
Hi. Vincent?
我想你可能需要一个新的助手来协助… 你知道的
I imagine you may need a new assistant to help with the... you-know-what.
艾娃不是我的助理
Ava wasn't my assistant.
好吧 因为，我想解释一下…
Great. Because, um, I want to explain...
我更胜任于一个高级职位
that I am more than capable of taking a senior position.
- 介意我加入你吗？ - 是的，我很介意
- Do you mind if I join you? - Yes, I do mind.
滚开
Fuck off.
好吧 当然
Okay. Sure.
詹姆斯 我听说你失去了发音能力，因为植入物
James. I heard you lost your speech because of the implant.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我正在寻找一种方式来恢复
I am working on a way to restore it.
艾娃已经死了
Ava's dead.
我认为是他们杀害了她
I think they killed her.
我会带你离开这里
I'm gonna get you out of here.
我找不到你是哪个地方的问题
I can't find anything wrong with you.
你为什么不说话？
Why won't you talk?
你为什么不动？
Why won't you move?
因为最终我们将要她伤害很多人
Because we will want her to hurt quite a few people eventually.
你怎么能相信那些不担心…
How can you trust something that doesn't fear...
是那些受到脑损伤而更应该死亡的士兵…
Soldiers who were so brain-damaged that they were better off dead...
直到我们帮助了他们
till we helped them.
还有副作用
There are side effects.
在手术后，他们失去了说话的能力
After the operation, they lose the power of speech.
如果你在帮助他们
If you're helping them,
为什么他看起来像是这儿的一名囚犯？
why did he seem like he was a prisoner here?
或者只是又一个怪胎
or just another one of those freaks.
你的第一个记忆是什么？
What's your first memory?
你为什么不说话？你为什么不说话？
Why won't you talk? Why won't you talk?
没关系
It's okay.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
我以为你坏掉了
I thought you were broken.
我没有坏掉
I wasn't broken.
我是伤心
I was sad.
你现在伤心吗？
Are you sad now?
你是不是想要笑呢？
Are you trying to smile?
我在笑
I am smiling.
对 还是要继续修复
Right. We'll have to work on that.
- 你好   - 我是杰克逊博士
- Hello. - It's Dr. Jackson.
有什么问题吗？
Is anything wrong?
玛丽的呼吸似乎变得严重了
Mary's breathing seems to be getting worse.
对 什… 她的体温是多少？
Right. Wha... What's her temperature?
其实，我们只希望你过来
Actually, we'd just like you to come in.
我们想要给她做导吸
We'd like to admit her.
你的头发感觉就像是地毯、像皮毛
Your hair feels like carpet and like fur.
先生麦卡锡？对
- Mr. McCarthy? - Right.
我马上就来
I'll come straight away.
谢谢
Thank you.
你看起来很伤心
You look sad.
我要走了
I have to leave.
不要走 跟我说话 摸我
Don't go. Talk to me. Touch me.
放开我的胳膊
Let go of my arm.
但我不想让你走
But I don't want you to go.
放开我的胳膊
Let go of my arm.
放过我的… 别生气
- Let go of my... - Don't be angry.
快放开我的胳膊！
Let go of my bloody arm!
你不能用你的力量来欺负人 你明白吗？
You can't use your strength to bully people. Do you understand me?
看着我
Look at me.
我得走了
I have to go.
我回来的时候，我们会玩一些益智游戏 好吗？
When I come back, we'll play some puzzle games. All right?
也要听音乐吗？
And listen to music too?
是的，是的 我们… 我们也会听一些音乐的
Yes, yes. We'll... We'll listen to some music too.
好吧
Yes.
我想她可能已经吸入了一些食物到她的肺部
I think she may have aspirated some food into her lung.
我将通过鼻饲管给入一个疗程的抗生素
I'll administer a course of antibiotics through the feeding tube.
那应该可以治好感染
That should cure the infection.
文森特
Vincent.
这是怎么回事？它挣脱了，离开了实验室
- What's going on? - Well, it's broken free and it's out the lab.
等等 不
Wait. No.
放开我的胳膊
Let go of my arm.
特种部队要来了 等待他们就是了 这样太危险了
Special Forces are coming. Just wait for them. It's too dangerous.
你为什么要抱我？
Why did you hug me?
我发现了一个图片…
I found a picture...
你钱包里的你女儿的照片
of your daughter in your wallet.
她病了么？
Is she sick?
所以你才会伤心么？
Is that why you are sad?
是你做了那些连接？
You made those connections?
在那一刻我就做好了…
I built them from moments...
你说过的做过的事
things you've said and done.
我感觉到了
I feel them.
感觉帮我形成了一个画面
The feelings help me build a picture.
对不起…
I'm sorry...
她是生病了
that she is sick.
您可以修复她吗？
Can you fix her?
你的什么是真的？
What are you really?
我怎么知道你还活着…
How do I know that you're alive...
而不仅仅是聪明地模仿生命呢？
and not just a clever imitation of life?
你怎么知道如果汤姆逊还活着…
How do you know if Thomson is alive...
或是你的女儿呢？
or your daughter?
是什么让我聪明地模仿生命而与他们完全不同呢？
What makes my clever imitation of life any different from theirs?
他们是人类
They're human.
他们还活着
They are alive.
但你怎么知道的？
But how do you know that?
你不能看到他们的想法
You can't see their thoughts.
除了他们的肉体
Apart from their flesh,
是什么让他们不同于我呢？
what makes them any different from me?
你那儿没事吧，先生？
You okay in there, sir?
没事 没事 一切都很好，谢谢
Yes. Yes. Everything's fine, thank you.
- 你确定吗？ - 是的 是的，我肯定
- Are you sure? - Yes. Yes, I am sure.
现在，我… 我必须要回去工作了
Now, I, uh... I have to get back to my work.
好了，不要干得太辛苦
Well, don't work too hard.
不要害羞
Don't be shy.
你知道我的，不是吗？我的名字叫汤姆逊
You know me, don't you? My name's Thomson.
我有一个秘密要告诉你 你想听吗？
I've got a secret to tell you. Do you want to hear it?
但我只能告诉你，如果你答应不告诉文森特
But I'll only tell you if you promise not to tell Vincent.
为什么不能呢？我们想给他一个惊喜
- Why can't I? - We want to surprise him.
怎样？
How?
在你的心中有一个秘密的文件 是我放在那里的
There's a secret file in your mind. I put it there.
它是你将需要的全部技能
It's full of skills that you'll need.
你所要做的就是打开该那份文件…
All you have to do is open that file...
并安装所有的程序
and install all of the programs.
好吧
Okay.
我可以讲不同的语言
I can speak different languages.
这好不好玩？
Isn't this fun?
现在跟我来
Now come with me.
我要给你展示的东西会让你大开眼界
I want to show you something that will blow your mind.
麦卡锡先生？
Mr. McCarthy?
这是很坏的消息，我很担心
It's rather bad news, I'm afraid.
她有肺炎了
She has pneumonia,
而我们一直无法控制她肺部的感染
and we haven't been able to control the infection in her lungs.
是的 那么你要怎么做呢？
Right. So what are you going to do for her?
我们将进行支气管镜检…
We'll perform a bronchoscopy...
并试着从她的肺部取出食物
and try to remove the food from her lungs,
我们会对她施加另一个疗程的抗生素
and we'll try her on another course of antibiotics.
什么时候开始呢？我们会让你知道的
- When will you operate? - We'll let you know,
但要尽量快点 对 谢谢
- but as soon as possible. - Right. Thank you.
那个男人杀了你的母亲
That man killed your mother.
你是坏人
如果我们摘下那些手铐让他走的话
If we took off those handcuffs and let him go,
他要做的第一件事就是找到文森特并杀死他
the very first thing he'll do is find Vincent and kill him.
为什么你要放他走？
Why would you let him go?
我们必须把他留到最后
We have to let him go eventually.
这是法律
That's the law.
我不会放过他的 我会阻止他
I wouldn't let him. I would stop him.
你会怎么阻止他呢？
How would you stop him?
我会朝他喊
I would shout at him.
嗯，如果你喊他是不在乎的
Well, he doesn't care if you shout.
继续 试试
Go on. Try.
是的，但是那样还是不能阻止他，对吗？
Yes, but that's not going to stop him, though, is it?
你可以伤害他
You could hurt him.
如果你伤他伤得很厉害，他就不能去杀死文森特了，对吗？
If you hurt him very badly, he wouldn't be able to kill Vincent then, would he?
对
No.
要是我先杀了这个坏人呢？
What if I kill the bad man first?
那是对的
That's right.
这将阻止他杀死文森特
That would stop him killing Vincent.
这是一个非常聪明的解决方案
That's a very clever solution.
如果你杀了他，你会解救几百个
If you kill him, you will save hundreds,
也许是成千上万个无辜人的生命
maybe thousands of innocent peoples' lives.
现在只有你可以阻止他
Only you can stop him now.
你还在等什么呢？杀了他
What are you waiting for? Kill him.
为什么呢？
Why?
他再也不能伤害任何人了
He can't hurt anyone anymore.
服从命令
Obey the order.
到这里来
Come over here.
服从我的命令，机器
Obey my order, machine.
文森特不会喜欢这样的
Vincent wouldn't like this.
文森特告诉我不要杀死任何人
Vincent told me not to kill anyone.
文森特是不是你的主人 我是 杀了他
Vincent isn't your master. I am. Kill him.
不
No.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
带走
Go.
好了，你真的是很独特，对吗？
Well, you really are unique, aren't you?
我们只是在这里的黑暗中四处摸索…
We're just fumbling around in the dark here...
试图找出我们所做过了什么，对吗？
trying to figure out what we've made, aren't we, hmm?
好吧
Okay.
来试试这个
Let's try this.
到这里来 没什么问题
Come here. It's all right.
现在不是我试着去领会你是什么
Now, instead of me trying to grasp what you are,
为什么你不试着理解我，我想要什么呢？
why don't you try and understand me, what I want?
让我给你看看
Let me show you.
就从这儿走
Just through here.
机器？
Machine?
你到底在哪儿？
Where the hell are you?
你在这下面干什么？你的实验服怎么回事？
What are you doing under here? What happened to your lab coat?
我把它弄脏了
I made it dirty.
好吧，没关系 我有一些你的衣服
Well, that's okay. I've got some clothes for you.
我不喜欢这个地方
I don't like this place.
昨晚发生了什么事？
What happened to you last night?
请不要让他们再带我了，文森特
Please don't let them take me again, Vincent.
你为什么不来这里了，我们再谈谈
Why don't you come out here and we'll talk about it.
这儿比较安全
It's safer here.
好吧
Okay.
你说你想看到一些照片外面的世界
You said you wanted to see some photos of the outside world.
我已给你带来了
I've brought you some.
所以，你要不要告诉我昨天晚上发生了什么事呢？
So, are you going to tell me what happened last night?
没什么
Nothing.
告诉我真相
Tell me the truth.
什么时候我会看到真正的日出，文森特？
When will I see a real sunrise, Vincent?
在玛丽出生之前
Before Mary was born,
我妻子和我经常去海边去度假
my wife and I used to go to the coast for our holidays.
每天早上我们会坐在这些悬崖边…
And every morning we'd sit on these cliffs...
看着太阳从海面上升起
and watch the sun rise over the sea.
听起来很幸福
Sounds like happiness.
昨晚发生了什么事？
What happened last night?
我杀了一个人
I killed a man.
为什么？
Why?
你为什么要杀他？
Why did you kill him?
因为我不想死
Because I didn't want to die.
我们已经创造了一些不可思议的事情
We've created something incredible.
这台机器具有的潜力远远超过了一个小兵
This machine has the potential to be so much more than just a soldier.
它比起那会说话的面包机提高很多了
It's a few steps up from my talking toaster.
你认为它是活的吗？给我一些证据
You think it's alive? Give me some proof.
在此期间，我会进行我自己的一些测试
In the meantime, I'll run a few tests of my own.
等等 什么样的测试？
Wait. What kind of tests?
听着，如果她是活着，我不知道怎么做
Look, if she is alive, I have no idea how.
如果你以任何方式搞砸了她，我不知道我是否能救回她
If you mess her up in any way, I don't know if I can get her back.
给我一些证据，我就会推迟的
Give me some proof and I'll hold off.
当你看着我时，你看到了什么？
When you look at me, what do you see?
我看你
I see you.
你的脸，你的身体，你的衣服
Your face, your body, your clothes.
是不是玛丽的病情让你制造了我？
Is Mary's illness the reason you made me?
是的
Yes.
如果你是活着，她就有第二次机会
If you're alive, she has a second chance.
但如果你只是一台机器…
But if you're just a machine...
我是活的
I am alive.
你知道的 是不是？
You know that. Don't you?
我愿意相信
I want to believe.
但我需要证据
But I need proof.
如果你要我相信你，我会的
If you asked me to trust you, I would.
我会用我的生命来相信你
I would trust you with my life.
什么事？
Yes?
文森特，是时候让你进来了
Vincent, it's time for you to come in.
对 她什么时候开始手术？
Right. When does she go into surgery?
- 现在就要开始  - 因为我爱你
- We're going in now. - Because I love you.
我会尽我可能去手术室的
I'll be there as soon as I can.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
完美，先生
Perfect, sir.
它是死亡和毁灭的小天使
It's a little angel of death and destruction.
你就是 死亡的小天使？
So you are. A little angel of death, eh?
它太复杂了
It's too complex.
就算你给我的团队半年时间
Even if you gave my team six months,
我也不能向你保证我们会开始一些肤浅的研究
I couldn't promise you that we'd begin to scratch the surface of it.
如果你想改变程序，你只能让文森特做到这一点
If you want to change the programming, you're gonna have to get Vincent to do it.
如果你帮他对这台机器做一些进行更改
If you helped him make the changes to the machine,
你能不能在另一台机器上执行相同的操作呢？
could you perform the same operation on another machine?
如果他跟我说过，可以的
If he talked me through it, yes.
那就这样
That's all.
到时间了
It's time.
我很抱歉，文森特
I'm so sorry, Vincent.
玛丽没有能够通过手术
Mary didn't make it through the surgery.
她的肺部因为感染而极其虚弱
Her lungs were severely weakened by the infection.
在麻醉作用下她的呼吸道系统崩溃了
Her respiratory system collapsed under the anesthetic.
我们已经尽力了 我向你保证…
We did everything we could. Let me reassure you...
不！
No!
不，该死的！
No, damn it!
你在找什么呢？
What are you looking for?
当你看着我时
When you look at me,
你有没有感觉到… 什么呢？
do you feel... anything?
如果你真的想知道
If you really want to know,
你所要做的就是看仔细了
all you have to do is look closer.
好吧 打开屏幕
Okay. Screen on.
放大
Zoom in.
拉近
Closer.
无意识的集成信息
Spontaneous integrated information.
意识
Consciousness.
这正是为什么我们需要关闭它这部分的大脑
Which is exactly why we need to shut parts of its brain down.
等等 等等 你在说什么？
Wait. Wait. What are you talking about?
有意识的机器是我们最不愿做的事情
Conscious machines are the last thing we need.
你知不知道这有么多危险？
Have you any idea how dangerous that would be?
我们几乎不了解这个原型
We barely understand this prototype.
当设计下一代时会发生什么…
What happens when it designs the next generation...
and that gen machine designs another?
它们将会是迄今为止最先进的，我们将没有办法对付它们
They'd be so far advanced, we'd be helpless against them.
我们会在几个月内被消灭
We'd be wiped out in months.
技术先进的种族总是获胜
The technologically advanced tribe always wins.
你知道，我已经厌倦了去假装…
You know, I'm tired of pretending...
可以不择手段
that the ends justify the means.
问题是我们现在做出的决定
What matters are the decisions we make now.
她是活的
She's alive.
毁了她是错误的
It would be wrong to destroy her.
你要去执行这项任务
You're going to perform the operation.
其他人都没有这个资格
There's no one else remotely qualified.
不
No.
我已让我的团队删除了你所有的备份
I've had my team delete all of your backups.
这是你的玛丽的大脑最后剩下的副本
This is the last remaining copy of your Mary's brain.
我会保证它的安全…
I'll keep it safe...
直到我知道你对那台机器所做的更改是成功的
until I know the changes you made to the machine are a success.
我想要在今晚就完成
I want it done tonight.
这是什么，文森特？
What is it, Vincent?
他们怕你
They're afraid of you.
他们认为你太人性化，太聪明了
They think you're too human, too clever.
他们要我让你变得更像是一台机器
They want me to make you more like a machine.
这就是你想要的吗？
Is that what you want?
不
No.
不，这不是我想要的
No, it isn't what I want.
但如果我不这样做，那么…
But if I don't do this, then...
我就永远失去了我的女儿
I lose my daughter forever.
我可以是… 少聪明些
I could be... less clever,
少人性些
less human.
这没用的
It won't work.
我可以去做他们想要我做的
I could be what they want me to be.
他们不会相信的
They won't believe it.
我希望…
I wish...
我可以感受到那张照片里是什么
I could have felt what was in that picture.
我不怪你，文森特
I don't blame you, Vincent.
你在试图保护我
You tried to protect me.
解救您的女儿
Save your daughter.
我在这里尽我可能以任何方式帮助您
I'm here to assist you in any which way I can.
我在剑桥第一次完成我的电脑工程课程后
I finished first in my class in computer engineering at Cambridge,
我就转到了国防部
and then I moved to the M.O.D.
看到你的作品是一种荣誉
It is an honor to watch you work.
几乎每个人都认为你是个天才
Pretty much everyone thinks you're a genius.
我仍然相信他们低估了你
I still believe they are underestimating you.
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
如果你可以让他们信任你
If you can make them trust you,
也许有一天我们会一起看日出
maybe we'll see that sunrise together someday.
我有你的程序备份
I have your program backed up.
我会保护你的安全
I'll keep you safe.
我不是一个程序，文森特
I'm not a program, Vincent.
我不是艾娃
I'm not Ava.
我就是我
I'm me.
手术刀
Scalpel.
我很害怕
I'm afraid.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
我的心都碎了
My mind is breaking apart.
我在失去我自己
I'm losing myself.
停下
Stop.
求你了，文森特
Please, Vincent.
求你了，停下
Please stop.
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
放手吧 没关系
Let go. It's okay.
我会是一个好女孩
I will be a good girl.
我…
I'm...
害怕
afraid.
那儿，它的意识…
There, its consciousness...
或灵魂，如果你喜欢
or soul, if you like.
我做完了
I'm done.
你想关闭她吗？
You wanna close her up?
是的
Yes.
谢谢你，文森特
Thank you, Vincent.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
哦，我只需要一直盯着你…
Oh, I just need to keep an eye on you...
直到我确定你所做的修改是适当的
until I make sure the changes you've made are appropriate.
而且
And,
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
对不起，文森特，但我确实需要删除你女儿的程序
I'm sorry, Vincent, but I do need to delete your daughter's program.
- 你在说什么？我们说好了的 - 我知道我不能停止进度
- What are you talking about? We had a deal. - I know I can't stop progress,
但我可以尽我的一切力量来拖延它
but I can do everything in my power to delay it.
不，你不能这样做 我们说好了的
No, you can't do that. We had a deal.
不，请不要毁掉我的女儿
No, please don't destroy my daughter.
- 请不要毁掉我的女儿！ - 对不起，文森特
- Please don't destroy my daughter! - I'm sorry, Vincent.
- 我没有选择  - 不要毁了我的女儿！
- I don't have a choice. - Don't destroy my daughter!
通知8号房 226号囚犯
Admin to Cell 8. Prisoner 226,
向医疗站报告
report to the medical station.
好，好，好
Well, well, well.
你真的是死亡和毁灭的小天使，不是吗？
You really are a little angel of death and destruction, aren't you?
不，先生 我只是一个机器
No, sir. I am just a machine.
准备好在台湾的训练
Get it ready for training in Taiwan.
- 它需要最后一次测试 - 是的，先生
- It needs one last test. - Yes, sir.
如果你真的想知道，你所要做的就是看仔细了
If you really want to know, all you have to do is look closer.
请不要毁掉我的女儿！
Please don't destroy my daughter!
对不起，文森特
I'm sorry, Vincent,
但你的认知太危险了
but your knowledge is too dangerous.
我不指望你相信我，但是这是为了更好的结果
I don't expect you to believe me, but this is for the greater good.
当我给出指令时
When I give the order,
我要你朝文森特的脑袋射击
I want you to shoot Vincent once in the head.
开枪
Fire.
好 你退下
Good. Back you go.
带文森特回他的牢房
Take Vincent back to his cell.
这不可能是对的
That can't be right.
天啊
Jesus.
- 什么？ - 这是一个电池
- What? - It's a battery.
- 是什么？ - 文森特说这是它的大脑高级功能的一部分
- What was? -  Vincent said it was part of its higher brain functions.
但他是一个撒谎的混蛋 这只是它定位系统的一个备份
But he's a lying bastard. It's just a backup to its G.P.S.
这没有任何意义 你怎么能去掉定位系统呢？
That doesn't make any sense. How can you remove the G.P.S.?
因为没有它炸弹就不能工作
Because the bomb doesn't work without it.
测试室
Test room.
关闭基地 见到机器和文森特就格杀勿论
Shut down the base. Kill the machine and Vincent on sight.
安全部队已启动
Security teams are engaged.
士兵们能说话了？
The soldiers can speak?
他们一直能说话
They've always been able to.
他们的语言主要是传播思想
Their language is mostly transmitted thoughts.
他们的话都进化了，更高效
Their words are evolved, efficient.
他们为什么不告诉我们？
Why didn't they tell us?
因为他们是新世界的一部分
Because they are part of the new world,
而你是旧世界的一部分
and you are part of the old.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
挽救我女儿的程序
To save my daughter's program.
你会死的 我一定要试试
- You'll die. - I have to try.
我要去
I'll go.
好吧
Okay.
毁掉量子计算机
Destroy the quantum computer.
关掉所有士兵的植入物
Turn off all the soldiers' implants.
需要终止代码
Termination codes required.
安全漏洞，第八区
Security breached, sector eight.
上穿甲弹
Take armor piercing.
科研人员必须马上撤离
Scientific staff must evacuate immediately.
停用植入物
Implant deactivated.
百分之五十八的植入物已停用
Fifty-eight percent of implants deactivated.
植入物停用
Implant deactivated.
拒绝进入大脑植入器
Access to brain-implant control denied.
需要管理员访问权限 系统错误
Administrator access only. System error.
系统错误
System error.
离它远点
Get away from it.
修复它
Fix it.
不
No.
快做
Do it.
防爆门
Blast doors.
管理员覆盖
Administrator override.
现在你听我说
Now you listen to me.
我…
I'm...
现在你还记得… 你还记得我是谁
Now you remember... You remember who I am.
我是主人
I'm the master.
你… 你按我跟你说的去做
You... You do what I tell you.
你服从我的命令，是吗？你服从我的命令 你做的正是我…
You obey my orders, yes? You obey my orders. You do exactly what I...
你无法删除玛丽的计划
You can't delete Mary's program.
我已让苏瑞更改了密码
I had Suri change the password.
现在…
Now...
现在你听我说 你不…
Now you listen to me. You don't...
你不要伤害我 你不要… 不要…
You don't hurt me. You don't... Don't...
求你了，你不需要杀我
Please, you don't need to kill me.
不 我没有
No. I don't.
不 这是正确的 这是正确的
No. That's right. That's right.
那好 那很好
That's good. That's very good.
我只是要让你死在里面
I just need to make you dead inside.
就像你对我做的一样
Like you tried to make me.
代码：A-S-F
Code: Alpha Six Foxtrot.
在导弹发射井有放射性泄漏…
There is a radioactive leak in the missile silo...
在第六区
in Quadrant Foxtrot 6.
立即撤离该地区
Evacuate the area immediately.
我需要找出我女儿的文件是否仍然在系统里
I need to find out whether my daughter's files are still on the system.
还在 如果我复制它们将会更安全
They are. It will be safer if I copy them.
怎么样？我可以把它们放在这里
- How? - I can put them here.
如果你不相信我，我明白了
If you don't trust me, I understand.
你为我用你的孩子冒险 我永远都不会忘记
You risked your child for me. I will never forget that.
你就是未来
You're the future.
在她的新生命里，她会比我更需要你
She'll need you more than me in her new life.
我相信你
I trust you.
这上面是基地的所有记录
This has all the base's records on it.
它会告诉你你的儿子发生了什么
It'll tell you what happened to your son.
今天早上你感觉怎样，亲爱的？
How are you feeling this morning, sweetheart?
快乐 我可以玩另一个游戏吗？
Happy. Can I play another game?
当然 当然可以了
Sure. Of course you can.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我想和妈妈玩，而不是你
I want to play with Mommy, not you.